https://www.peaksensors.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Privacy, Security and CookiesYou are here: Home1 / Privacy, Security and CookiesSummary of PoliciesWe don’t disclose information to third parties unless legally required to do so.We don’t sell or rent personal information.We use some cookies, but you can opt-out below.By using this site you agree to these policies.Privacy PolicyPeak Sensors respects the privacy of its customers, suppliers, and website visitors. We never sell personal data and we carry out all processing operations in strict compliance with the EU General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”). This page describes the information we collect, how we obtain the information and how we may use that information.Customers and SuppliersWhat information does Peak Sensors collect?We collect basic information when you trade with us such as your name, email address and phone number.If you are a private individual and not a business, we may also collect your private address and payment information if you provide it. For example, if you are a private individual and order from our online store we will collect your address and payment card information in order to fulfil your online order.We also keep records when you contact us such as email communication.How does Peak Sensors use information about me?We use information about you to fulfil our obligations to you as either a customer or supplier, or to comply with other legal or regulatory obligations. For example, we use email information to provide order acknowledgements, quotes or invoices as we have a legitimate interest in doing so because of our existing business relationship.We will only contact you if we believe we have legitimate interest in doing so. If you have any problems with Peak Sensors contacting you please e-mail a request to stop communication or change the methods of our communication, or you can unsubscribe from non-transactional emails from us at the bottom of the email.Does Peak Sensors share my data with third parties?We never share any of your data to third parties apart from when it is part of the order fulfilment process. For example, we may share your email address with a courier to enable you to receive delivery tracking of your order.Your Data, Your Rights and Opting outUnder certain circumstances, you have rights under data protection laws in relation to your personal data.[Request access to your personal data].[Request correction of your personal data].[Request erasure of your personal data].[Object to processing of your personal data].[Request restriction of processing your personal data].[Request transfer of your personal data].[Right to withdraw consent].If you wish to exercise any of the rights set out above, please contact us.No fee usually requiredYou will not have to pay a fee to access your personal data (or to exercise any of the other rights). However, we may charge a reasonable fee if your request is clearly unfounded, repetitive or excessive. Alternatively, we may refuse to comply with your request in these circumstances.What we may need from youWe may need to request specific information from you to help us confirm your identity and ensure your right to access your personal data (or to exercise any of your other rights). This is a security measure to ensure that personal data is not disclosed to any person who has no right to receive it. We may also contact you to ask you for further information in relation to your request to speed up our response.Time limit to respondWe try to respond to all legitimate requests within one month. Occasionally it may take us longer than a month if your request is particularly complex or you have made a number of requests. In this case, we will notify you and keep you updated.Credit Card SecurityWhen an order is placed at our website or on the telephone, credit card numbers are encrypted and transmitted using 256 bit encryption to SagePay. Sage pay is audited annually under the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standards (PCI DSS) and is a fully approved payment services provider (PSP). We never see your credit card number and they are not held in clear text on any web site or database. It’s that simple. To view Sage Pay’s security policy click here.Website Cookies and Tracking Technologies – How to Opt OutWe use some unobtrusive cookies to store information on your computer.Some cookies on this site are essential, and the site won’t work as expected without them. These cookies are set when you submit a form, login or interact with the site by doing something that goes beyond clicking on simple links.Non-essential Cookies we use include:Google Analytics CookiesGoogle Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of this website, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services. Google may use the Data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.If you would like to opt-out of Google Analytics visit this page.Google Remarketing CookiesWe may use Google Remarketing to connect with you, based upon your past interactions with this site. As a result Google may show Peak Sensors Ltd ads on sites you visit on the internet. Google use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to our website.If you would like to opt-out of Google Remarketing visit this page.Statistical Usage DataWe may collect information about your computer, including where available your session data, operating system and browser type, for system administration and marketing activities. This is statistical data about our users’ browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual or IP address. We do not share this information with any third parties.If you would like to opt-out of this tracking visit this page.Your acceptance of these termsBy using this website, you signify your agreement to the Peak Sensors privacy policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use this website. From time to time we may update our policies in line with website changes that may affect the personal information we gather about you. It is assumed that you accept such changes if you continue to use the site and services.Recent Blog Posts Peak Sensors Achieve Another Year ISO 9001 Certified Peak Sensors joins the Made in Britain Community Russian Glass Plant Improves Performance   Peak Sensors Ltd, The Bridge, Beresford Way, Chesterfield, S41 9FG, United Kingdom  +44 (0) 1246 261999  websales@peaksensors.comwww.peaksensors.co.ukInformationAbout UsContact UsWhat Our Customers SayGlobal AgentsVacanciesProductsThermocouplesResistance Thermometers/Pt100 SensorsOnline StoreSensor ServicesResourcesIndustries we supplyTemperature Sensor ResourcesISO 9001 ApprovalCredit ApplicationTemperature Sensor Blog Scroll to topThis site uses cookies. By continuing to browse the site, you are agreeing to our use of cookies.OKLearn moreCookie and Privacy SettingsHow we use cookiesWe may request cookies to be set on your device. We use cookies to let us know when you visit our websites, how you interact with us, to enrich your user experience, and to customize your relationship with our website.Click on the different category headings to find out more. You can also change some of your preferences. Note that blocking some types of cookies may impact your experience on our websites and the services we are able to offer.Essential Website CookiesThese cookies are strictly necessary to provide you with services available through our website and to use some of its features.Because these cookies are strictly necessary to deliver the website, refuseing them will have impact how our site functions. You always can block or delete cookies by changing your browser settings and force blocking all cookies on this website. But this will always prompt you to accept/refuse cookies when revisiting our site.We fully respect if you want to refuse cookies but to avoid asking you again and again kindly allow us to store a cookie for that. You are free to opt out any time or opt in for other cookies to get a better experience. If you refuse cookies we will remove all set cookies in our domain.We provide you with a list of stored cookies on your computer in our domain so you can check what we stored. Due to security reasons we are not able to show or modify cookies from other domains. You can check these in your browser security settings.Check to enable permanent hiding of message bar and refuse all cookies if you do not opt in. We need 2 cookies to store this setting. Otherwise you will be prompted again when opening a new browser window or new a tab.Click to enable/disable essential site cookies.Other external servicesWe also use different external services like Google Webfonts, Google Maps, and external Video providers. Since these providers may collect personal data like your IP address we allow you to block them here. Please be aware that this might heavily reduce the functionality and appearance of our site. Changes will take effect once you reload the page.Google Webfont Settings:Click to enable/disable Google Webfonts.Google Map Settings:Click to enable/disable Google Maps.Google reCaptcha Settings:Click to enable/disable Google reCaptcha.Vimeo and Youtube video embeds:Click to enable/disable video embeds.Privacy PolicyYou can read about our cookies and privacy settings in detail on our Privacy Policy Page. Privacy, Security and CookiesAccept settingsHide notification only
